[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":72430,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":82194,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":7256,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":89453,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":15142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":104598,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":8434,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":113034,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":9235,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":122270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":5495,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":127767,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second  one to i t. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1","0"],"rt":11315,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":139083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":5356,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":144441,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":6100,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":150543,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":2242,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":152786,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":156191,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<s ub>6</su b> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":979,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":157172,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":3082,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":160254,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":865,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":161119,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br  /><br />  (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":2554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":163674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":2069,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":165743,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your re sult.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":3626,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":169370,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1707,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":171079,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":2243,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":173322,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":903,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":174226,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":2284,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":176511,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":856,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":177367,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":14352,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":191721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inve rse unde r +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":51263,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":242985,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":16829,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":259817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":6293,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":266111,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br / ><br />  (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["5"],"rt":5607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":271719,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1828,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":273548,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":1878,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":275427,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1109,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":276537,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["45","4"],"rt":6794,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":283331,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity  under +< sub>6</sub>.","rt":1712,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":285044,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":6191,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":291237,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":19871,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":311108,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can  simply  be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":21987,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":333096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub> 6</sub>  2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":40911,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":374008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":11904,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":385914,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":12789,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":398705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br  /><br />  (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":6245,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":404951,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":46665,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":451617,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4 a generator under +<sub >6</sub> ? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":32041,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":483660,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":19673,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":503334,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["No"],"rt":3380,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":506716,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":3120,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":509836,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedbac k to mak e sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the remaining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":37399,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":547236,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1"],"rt":7523,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":554761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":1699,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":556461,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["6"],"rt":4309,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":560770,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2"],"rt":5621,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":566392,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":4072,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":570465,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":3522,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":573988,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["3"],"rt":3531,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":577520,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"On the following question, and several others later in the HIT, we will ask you to explain how you got your answer. On these questions, you will be given one box for your answer to the question, and a second for your explanation. Please explain your thought process in as much detail as possible (at least one sentence, and more if you can).","rt":11817,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":589339,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":" What is  4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","explain":true,"explanation":"4 plus 1 equals 5 and it is less than 8 so you don't subtract.","explanation_history":["The ","The","Th","T","4 and 1 e","4 and 1 ","4 and 1","4 and ","4 and","4 an","4 a","4 plus 1 equals 5 and it is less than 98","4 plus 1 equals 5 and it is less than 9","4 plus 1 equals 5 and it is less than 8 so you don't subra","4 plus 1 equals 5 and it is less than 8 so you don't subrr","4 plus 1 equals 5 and it is less than 8 so you don't subr","4 plus 1 equals 5 and it is less than 8 so you don't subtract."],"response_history":["5"],"rt":44701,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":634043,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3 ","response":"3","explain":true,"explanation":"When the sum of the two numbers is greater than 8 you subtract 9 from the answer.","explanation_history":["When the sum of the two numbers is greater than 8 you subratc","When the sum of the two numbers is greater than 8 you subrat","When the sum of the two numbers is greater than 8 you subra","When the sum of the two numbers is greater than 8 you subr","When the sum of the two numbers is greater than 8 you subtract 9 from the answer."],"response_history":["3"],"rt":26750,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":660796,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":true,"explanation":"I think it is 0 because that's what I remember from the first operation.","explanation_history":["I think it is 0 because that's  what I r emembe ","I think it is 0 because that's what I remember from the first operation."],"response_history":["0"],"rt":56767,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":717564,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["4"],"rt":22726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":740293,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["7"],"rt":4143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":744438,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 und er +<sub >9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["0"],"rt":13698,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":758137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","explain":true,"explanation":"I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 0 and that is how you find the inverse.","explanation_history":["I added the number to 3 that would result in 9 ","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subrta","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subrt","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subr","I added the n umber to  3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 90","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 9","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 0.","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 0 and that is th","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 0 and that is t","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 0 and that is ","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 0 and that is","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9. I knew when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 0 and that i","I added the number to 3 that would result in 9.  I knew  when it was subtracted that it would be the identity 0 and that is how you find the inverse."],"response_history":["6"],"rt":59786,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":817925,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I don't think 2 fulfills the requirement for a generator.","explanation_history":["I don't think 2 fuf","I don't think 2 fulfills the rqu","I don't think 2 fulfills the rq","I don't think 2 fulfills the requirement for a generator. 2","I don't think 2 fulfills the requirement for a generator. ","I don't think 2 fulfills the requirement for a generator."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":78842,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":896769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and it doesn't seem to add up. I don't believe it is a generator.","explanation_history":["I' ","I'm trying to do the math for te ","I'm trying to do the math for te","I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and I ","I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and I","I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and it doesn't seem to m","I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and it doesn't seem to add up ","I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and it doesn't seem to add up. I don't believe it is a genator","I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and it doesn't seem to add up. I don't believe it is a genato","I'm trying  to do th e math for the generator in my head and it doesn't seem to add up. I don't believe it is a genat","I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and it doesn't seem to add up. I don't believe it is a gena","I'm trying to do the math for the generator in my head and it doesn't seem to add up. I don't believe it is a generator."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":85975,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":982747,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I have to answer no because I'm not sure.","explanation_history":["I havet ","I havet","I have to answer no because I ","I have to answer no because I'm not sure ","I have to answer no because I'm not sure."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":67077,"trial_type":"questio n","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1049826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","explain":true,"explanation":"I have to answer no because I can't recall much about generators now.","explanation_history":["I Hav","I Ha","I H","I have to answer no because I can't recall much about generators now."],"response_history":["No"],"rt":162732,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1212561,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary  value if  necessary.","rt":55707,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1268269,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"I'm not sure. +n minus 1 equals the inverse.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I'm not sure. -","I'm not sure. =n","I'm not sure. =","I'm not sure. +n minus 1 equals the inverse."],"rt":98458,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1366729,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I don't know","explain":true,"explanation":"I'm not sure.","explanation_history":["I'm not sure."],"response_history":["I' m ","I'm","I'","I","I'm not sure ","I do'","I don't know"],"rt":48514,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1415245,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can tell.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I can't think of any pattern. I don","I can't think of any pattern. I do","I can't think of any pattern. I d","I can't think of any pattern. I ","I can't think of any pattern. I'm nto ","I can't think of any pattern. I'm nto","I can't think of any pattern. I'm nt","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see weht","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see  weh","I  can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see we","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whether there is ","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whether there is","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whether there i","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whether there ","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whether ","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whether","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whethe","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see wheth","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whet","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see whe","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see wh","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see w","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can see ","I can't think of any pa ttern. I 'm not sure how you can see","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can se","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can s","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can tel.","I can't think of any pattern. I'm not sure how you can tell."],"rt":112119,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1527365,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":9387,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1536753,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":7630,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1544385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["False"],"rt":12457,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1556843,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"True","response":"Fals e","explain":true,"explanation":"I put false because I'm not sure of the answer at all.","explanation_history":["I put false because I'm not sure.","I put false because I'm not sure of the answer at all."],"response_history":["False"],"rt":43110,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1599954,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Always","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Always"],"rt":36917,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1636872,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Ple ase expl ain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Sometimes","response":"Never","explain":true,"explanation":"I think the answer would be 0 and they can't be generators.","explanation_history":["I think the answer would be 0","I think the answer would be 0 s","I think the answer would be 0 and they can't g","I think the answer would be 0 and they can't be gent","I think the answer would be 0 and they can't be generators."],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":45259,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1682133,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Never"],"rt":16216,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1698351,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1990,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1700342,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["29"],"rt":3751,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1704093,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Mas ters Deg ree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":3897,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1707990,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Trignometry","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Algebra ","Algebra","Trignometry"],"rt":55315,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1763306,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't kno w what i t was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":5129,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1768437,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":3290,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1771729,"internal_chunk_id":" 0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":5285,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1777015,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat"],"rt":9108,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1786123,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - som ewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":4970,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1791094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["Male"],"rt":2176,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1793270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["English"],"rt":8807,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1802077,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"no","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["no"],"rt":4770,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1806849,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions and concepts, I was confused with generators and couldn't remember exactly how to imagine them in my head. It was tough.","explain":false,"explanation":"","explanation_history":[],"response_history":["I think there should have been a way to refresh ","I think there should have been a way to re","I think there should have been a way to r"," I think  there should have been a way to ","I think there should have been a way to","I think there should have been a way t","I think there should have been a way to look at the basic definitions of ","I think there should have been a way to look a","I think there should have been a way to look bak ","I think there should have been a way to look bak","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in order to ","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in order t","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in order ","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in order","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in orde","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in ord","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in or","I think there should have been a way to  look bac k at the basic definitions in o","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in ","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions in","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions i","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions ","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions and concepts, I got a bit confuse","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions and concepts, I got","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions and concepts, I go","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions and concepts, I g","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions and concepts, I was confused with generators and couldn't remember exactly how to imag ine them  in my head. It wa ","I think there should have been a way to look back at the basic definitions and concepts, I was confused with generators and couldn't remember exactly how to imagine them in my head. It was tough."],"rt":110607,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":88,"time_elapsed":1917456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]